Front-end Developer

Nur Fikri Kiki (He/Him)

https://kikiding.space

kikiding.space@gmail.com

https://github.com/codingki

I currently live in Yogyakarta, Indonesia (+7 UTC). I'm 24 years old. Now I'm studying at Amikom Yogyakarta 6th semester. I'm a Front-end developer. React and React native is my main tools for building apps. I can describe my self as a designer who trapped in the mind of a programmer, I love building modern and beautiful app.

Education

University, Courses, Certifications etc.

Purwadhika, Tangerang, Indonesia (2016-2017)

Amikom University, Yogyakarta, Indonesia (2019-present)

Skills

Javascript, Typescript, React, React native, Next.js, Electron, Figure

Experience

Front-end Developer @ Accelbyte

Apr 2021 - Present, Yogyakarta/Remote

[Electron, React, Typescript]

Work with both internal and client's engineering teams to help design, advise, and deliver a user interface for both internal and external use that is highly functional, responsive, and lightweight based on UX design and backend APIs.

React Native Developer @ Freelance

Aug 2017 - Mar 2021, Remote

[React Native, Expo, Typescript]
Deliver user interface from client requests.
Building cross platform mobile applications (IOS, Android)

Awards, Featured Project

Second Place BNCC Technoscape X Tiket.com Hackathon (BINUS)

12 Okt 2020

[React Native, Expo, Javascript]
Creating mobile apps: An online concert ticket sales platform that can be purchased seperately (ketengan)
https://github.com/codingki/TikTeng

React Native Rapi UI

2021

[React Native, Expo, Typescript, Figma]
Rapi UI is a UI components library for react native https://rapi-ui.kikiding.space

Kawalcovid19.id

2021

[React, Styled components, Typescript]
Contribute to design, code and connecting the APIs the vaccine rubric for kawalcovid19.id. also vaccine widget on the home page
https://kawalcovid19.id/vaksin

React Native Expo starter templates

2020

[React Native, Typescript, Firebase, Supabase]
Starter templates that having a UI, Navigation, Auth for React
Native + Expo
https://rapi-ui.kikiding.space